[footsteps approaching]
[CHA] An E-rank hunter
taking a carrier job
in an A-rank dungeon?
Does he think he's invincible?
What's his motive?
And I know what I saw.
He did have a weapon
when I caught him
in front of the boss room.
Something's up.
I'll be going in the gate, too.
[YOONSEOK]
Uh.
Why, did something
happen in there?
[CHA] No.
It's a personal matter.
Nothing for you to worry about.
[exhales sharply]
I'm sorry,
but do you have any weapons
I could borrow?
Uh.
Hmm.
Yeah, so...
I was hoping for
something more traditional.
Like a sword or a spear.
[YOONSEOK]
You know we're miners?
We've got shovels
and crowbars eh--
[CHA]
Never mind, thanks anyway.
I can fight just fine unarmed.
[YOONSEOK]
Think this through.
Do you really want to
go in empty handed?
♪
It may not be "traditional,"
but it's better
than nothing at all.
-[CHA] Very well.
-Hm.
[footsteps receding]
[flag rustles]
[thuds]
[banging]
♪
Look at 'em all.
If this many high orcs
ever broke out of here.
They would flatten
a city or two.
Long before help could arrive.
[GEONGUK]
Those four in particular.
They're packin' more aura
than the others.
A lot more.
[thuds]
♪
[KIHOON] It's our job
to close this gate.
We have to make sure
the dungeon boss goes down,
no matter what!
[fire crackling]
[KARGALGAN]
Do you fear me?
♪
Pitiful humans.
[gasps]
[GINA]
This can't be happening!
How does he have
so much magic power?
[BORA]
Compared to him,
it's like
I'm a third-rate spellcaster,
and that's being generous!
[shudders]
Well, we came to meet with you.
So, what now?
-[KARGALGAN] You entertain us.
-[KIHOON] Huh?
[KARGALGAN]
One by one,
you will be killed,
tortured, and devoured.
For the sole purpose
of pleasing my soldiers.
[all gasp]
Entertainment?
[KIHOON] That's all this beast
thinks we're good for?
He doesn't even
see us as enemies.
We're nothing
but toys to be broken...
and tossed aside.
[KARGALGAN]
Oh?
There's something strange
mixed with the humans.
This may be more interesting
than I thought.
[gasps]
Everyone, charge!
[all whimpering]
[breathes deeply]
[Kihoon screams]
[grunts]
[KARGALGAN]
Song of Guardian.
[sword clangs]
♪
[thuds]
[KARGALGAN]
You fool.
Antigravity.
[Kihoon groans]
[KARGALGAN]
Gravity Acceleration.
[thuds]
[groans]
Captain, no!
[thuds]
[Kihoon groans]
[Eunsoo breathes shakily]
Kihoon.
I'm sorry.
[crashes]
[whimpering]
[thuds]
[JINWOO]
Captain Son.
The Hunters Guild has
the rights to this dungeon.
It's really not my place, sir.
But as it stands
your strike team
is in real danger.
♪
So, let me ask you this...
[crashes]
[rumbling]
do I have your permission...
to kill every beast in here?
[breath trembles]
[whimpering]
Please do.
By all means.
[Kargalgan scoffs]
[KARGALGAN]
Just a copycat,
and no more intimidating
than a monkey.
[all gasp]
[JINWOO]
Gotta hand it to you.
You have the most intense aura
I've ever seen.
[KARGALGAN]
Naturally.
[JINWOO]
You know, unfortunately
this is a terrible matchup.
[all gasp]
[JINWOO]
And when I say that...
I mean for you.
[laughs]
[strains]
[exhales]
Huh?
The Surveillance Team?
[WORKER 1]
What are they doing here?
[WORKER 2]
How should I know?
Hey!
Someone call a supervisor!
[JINCHUL] He's worked two days
as a miner for them,
but what's his angle?
[YOONSEOK]
How can I help you gentlemen?
[JINCHUL] We're looking for
a hunter named Jinwoo Sung.
[YOONSEOK]
He sure is popular.
I freakin' knew it!
I knew that dude was sketchy!
You should've seen
the death glare he shot at me!
It was horrifying!
In fact, I thought
I was gonna die right there!
So, is he still around?
[YOONSEOK]
Yes, but inside the gate.
The carrier was a no-show,
so Sung stepped up to fill in.
[JINCHUL]
He isn't fighting?
[YOONSEOK]
No, sir.
[JINCHUL]
Went from mining the resources
to hauling the bags.
Being an S-rank means
everything he does
is subject to scrutiny.
-I hope he realizes that.
-[indistinct chatter]
There something
I should know about?
[JINCHUL]
I'm sure all will be revealed
on the news tomorrow.
-[LEE] The news?
-Hey, by the way,
Hunter Cha was
looking for him, too,
but didn't say why.
Hunter Cha was?
[all gasp]
[SURVEILLANCE MEMBER]
Oh, man!
That was one vicious aura!
[ASSOCIATE] Felt like it was
gonna tear me to shreds.
Quick, go measure
the gate's power!
-[SURVEILLANCE MEMBER]Yes, sir!
-[ASSOCIATE] Yes, sir!
[exhales]
[wind gusting]
[CHA]
I need to hurry.
How Kihoon's team was able
to beat this many high orcs
and then keep pressing on,
I don't know.
But if the blast of power
I just sensed
came from the boss.
I doubt
they'll be as lucky again.
[KARGALGAN]
Confronting my massive army
with your measly troop?
You brainless fool!
Don't look down on my guys,
it upsets me.
Monarch's Domain.
A skill exclusive
to my job class.
I got it after hitting level 70
in the Demon's Castle.
[roars]
Climbing the castle has made
my soldiers stronger, too.
The E-rank
summoned all of those things?
It doesn't make sense.
I can only manage two summons,
and that's on a good day.
[BORA]
His power feels almost inhuman.
♪
[KARGALGAN]
Kill them.
[all roar]
[roars]
[slices]
[scoffs]
[orcs groan]
[groans]
[orcs groaning]
[grunts]
[GEONGUK]
You see that?
It's like watching
the vice guildmaster fight.
Why is he carrying bags?
He could carry a strike team!
[slices]
[JINWOO] Most of my men
are around B-rank.
Each high orc's life
comes at the cost
of four or five of theirs.
So, I'll help thin the herd.
[KARGALGAN]
Song of Dragon Fire!
[Jinwoo gasps]
[fire roars]
[KARGALGAN] You believed those
scarecrows could save you?
Such arrogance.
Don't think you're one
to talk about arrogance.
'Cause my "scarecrows"
aren't done yet.
[KARGALGAN]
Song of Guardian.
Acceleration.
[crashes]
[grunts]
[KARGALGAN]
Gravity Acceleration.
[Jinwoo grunting]
[KARGALGAN]
Antigravity.
Acceleration.
[crashing]
[grunts]
[KARGALGAN]
You have limits,
so I'll kill your puppets
as many times as it takes.
Till your magic...
is spent!
Song of Fire!
[fire roaring]
[all panting]
[fire roars]
[JINWOO]
He's got a wellspring of mana
to fuel his ranged,
multi-target spells.
I can't get close.
[KARGALGAN]
I'm curious,
how long will it take
before you crumble?
[beeps]
[SURVEILLANCE MEMBER]
Results are in!
It turns out this gate
is a higher-end A-rank,
almost approaching S!
The first read was wrong, then.
Contact the guild's leader
ASAP.
The three of us
are going to head in
and provide the strike team
some backup.
[YOONSEOK]
R-right!
[KARGALGAN]
You see?
My soldiers are superior
in quantity and quality.
It's only a matter of time
before your magic power
is gone.
[smirks]
[JINWOO]
There you go again,
making assumptions.
[pops]
[gulps]
[JINWOO]
Heard of necromancers?
Well, how about I show you
one in action?
Arise.
[gasps]
[KARGALGAN]
Turning my soldiers into yours?
[JINWOO] They'll all become
my shadows soon enough.
And, of course.
So will you.
[Kargalgan growls]
[grunts]
[flag rustles]
[KARGALGAN]
How can this be?
He must be the...
Uh.
[groans]
But then why?
Why am I here?
What purpose do I serve?
When my eyes
first opened in this place,
there was but a single thought,
running through my head,
over and over again.
"Hunt...the humans."
The reason makes no difference.
I need only heed the command.
[orcs growling]
Your turn!
Slaughter the intruders.
And offer their carcasses
as a tribute to me!
[GUILD ASSOCIATE]
On par with an S-rank dungeon?
If the original measurement
had been accurate,
Hunter Son's team could've
cleared that gate,
but we were caught off guard.
Dreadfully so.
[GUILD ASSOCIATE]
A dungeon break could mean
Jeju Island part two.
[CHOI]
Thankfully, we still have time.
[elevator bell dings]
Gather our guild's
strongest forces.
We'll head there without delay.
The emergency call has already
gone out
to the Vice Guildmaster
and all of the A-ranks.
Worst-case scenario,
we could ask the White Tigers
or even the Reapers
-if they could give us a hand.
-[gasps]
Sir, if we do that...
Yes, I am well aware.
So, let's avoid it, shall we?
♪
[sword clanks]
[swords clanking]
[orc groans]
[orc roars]
[sword clanks]
[swords clanks]
[crashes]
It looks like my generals
have the upper hand here.
[KARGALGAN]
That's not possible.
C'mon, let's get in there!
-[SEOKJIN] Right!
-[GEONGUK] Hm.
[KARGALGAN] Song of High Fever!
Song of Blindness!
[vomits]
[KARGALGAN] The audience
should not presume
to take the stage.
And, truth be told...
I've had just about
enough of your insolence.
Song of Sleep!
Song of Impediment!
Song of Blindness!
What?
Nice try,
but I'm pretty resistant
to curses and poison.
[growls]
[KARGALGAN]
Song of Guardian!
[fire roars]
[JINWOO] All right, man,
I'm gonna break that
annoying shield of yours.
[gasps]
[explodes]
[bones clatter]
♪
[Kargalgan breathing heavily]
[CHA]
What's going on?
Are those being summoned here?
There are so many
of them though!
[BORA]
Vice Guildmaster!
Thank you for coming.
How's the captain?
He'll be okay.
That's great.
Hm.
Now, could one of you tell me
what I'm looking at?
[SEMI]
Honestly, we're confused, too.
[KARGALGAN]
How dare you?
Song of Rage!
Song of Strength!
Song of Giants!
Be crushed beneath my foot
like the insect you are!
[stomps]
[JINWOO]
Gotta say.
I'm not too fond of giants.
That move kinda pisses me off.
[KARGALGAN]
Song of Dragon Fire!
[fire roars]
[explodes]
♪
[orc groans]
[KARGALGAN]
Do you still think I,
the mighty Kargalgan,
am no match for you?
[JINWOO]
Yep.
[grunting]
[groans]
[JINWOO] The bigger the target,
the easier it is to hit.
[thuds]
[JINWOO]
You're a mage,
yet you thought
you could fend off
an assassin's attack
without your shield.
[groans]
[KARGALGAN]
Song of Fire!
[Jinwoo grunts]
[grunts]
[explodes]
[Jinwoo grunts]
[groans]
[exhales]
If daggers aren't enough,
let's try this!
[chain clinking]
[grunts]
[chain jingling]
[Kargalgan panting]
[grunts]
[Kargalgan breathing heavily]
[Jinwoo grunts]
[Jinwoo screams]
[thuds]
[breathes shakily]
[CHA]
Manager Woo?
Hunter Cha.
You're all safe.
We sensed a rather
alarming aura.
So, we rushed to help
as soon as we could.
But it seems Hunter Sung
had it under control.
[CHA]
Even the Surveillance Team
is onto him?
He's clearly
a top-class combat hunter,
but he uses summoning magic.
That's crazy.
How is he that strong?
Just who in the world
is that man?
I take it that
you've met him before?
Well, we are acquainted.
But only in passing.
[Kargalgan groans]
[JINWOO] The second your
bodyguards became mine.
You were as good as dead.
[KARGALGAN]
Do you know who I am?
My body can't
possibly be destroyed!
I'm invincible!
[grunts]
[grunting]
[thuds]
[breathes shakily]
[gasps]
♪
[buzzing]
[JINWOO]
I won't touch their loot,
even if I did solo the boss.
But,
I doubt they'll mind me
extracting his shadow.
Arise.
♪
[both gasp]
Glad to see becoming a shadow
chilled you out.
[scoffs]
A name?
Ah,
what was it?
Gargle, something.
I'm sorry, man,
how about I call you...
Tusk.
Yeah.
I like it.
Tusk.
[JINWOO]
"Elite Knight Rank?"
That's a new one.
Makes sense for an A-rank
dungeon boss, though.
These high orc guys
are pretty epic too.
Welcome to the team.
Hello, Hunter Sung.
[gasps]
[JINWOO]
Manager Woo?
I was too focused
on collecting shadows
to notice him!
[GEONGUK]
My man!
[SEMI] What was all that?
Aren't you a carrier?
[JINWOO]
I, well, uh...
What do I say?
Uh.
[JINCHUL]
That's classified information.
All matters
regarding Hunter Sung
have been deemed top secret,
and it's our job
to enforce that.
Which is why I need everyone
to keep what happened today
confidential.
We'll be escorting you out.
It's really the best way
to avoid
having any more
attention on you.
[JINWOO]
Hmm.
[JINCHUL]
I won't downplay the fact
that he has S-rank abilities,
you all saw that
with your own eyes.
But it's my hope
you'll make his exit quiet
in gratitude for your rescue.
[footsteps receding]
Just a minute, please!
I'm sure you have your reasons
for concealing
your real strength.
And, of course,
we have no right
to make you explain.
I'm not even gonna ask...
what made you take
the carrier job.
Point is,
a lot of lives
could have been lost
but instead,
we're all walking out of here,
and that's because of you.
As captain of this team,
you have my thanks.
[chuckles softly]
Oh!
That's right.
You want this back, yeah?
Huh!
[chuckles]
[JINCHUL] If you're finished,
let's get going.
[footsteps receding]
-[gasps]
-Um. Miss Cha?
Yes, Bora?
[BORA] I was just wondering
why you have a pickax?
[gasps]
Do you think I looked like
a weirdo to him?
[BORA]
By "him" you mean?
[CHA]
Never mind.
You can forget I asked that.
[CHOI]
It's a relief that everyone
made it out safely in the end.
But how odd,
Hunter Sung was there
for the White Tigers
and their red gate,
and then he came
to our rescue as well.
His speed is comparable
to an assassin type's,
he can raise the dead at will,
then add them
to his vast army of summons.
It's all a little hard
to believe.
In your honest,
unbiased opinion,
how does Hunter Sung
compare to me?
[gasps]
[exhales]
[KIHOON]
Hunters of different types
work together during raids,
pooling their strength
to compensate
for individual weaknesses.
It's standard
operating procedure.
Do you think you could clear
a higher-end A-rank dungeon
by yourself?
No tanks, no healers,
just you.
[exhales]
[CHOI]
No, I couldn't.
Which frankly
is rather embarrassing
considering all the talk of me
being the "ultimate weapon."
Heh.
Guildmaster...
[CHOI]
I know.
[KIHOON]
We need him.
[CHOI]
I'll do what I can.
[footsteps receding]
♪
-[JINHO] Yo, bro!
-Hm?
[chuckles]
♪
[JINWOO]
Sorry, it took me so long.
So, how'd the guildmaster
stuff go?
You work things out
with your dad?
[JINHO]
Funny you mention that.
Jinwoo.
I'd like to
run something by you.
I'm reporting live
-from the Hunter's Association.
-[MINSUNG] Ah, I'm loving this.
A flock of people
who swooped in just to see me.
"Minsung Lee,
the man who has it all,
has even acquired powers
that transcend
the human condition."
[chuckles]
[inhales deeply]
[sighs]
Man.
Not bad at all.
♪